<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright © 2022 TechNWeb, Inc. All rights reserved.
  ~ See TNW_LICENSE.txt for license details.
  -->

<config xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:magento:module:Magento_Store:etc/config.xsd">
    <default>
        <marketing>
            <products>
                <TNW_Subscriptions>
                    <label>mPower for Magento</label>
                    <img_name>subscription-management.png</img_name>
                    <description>Manage all your subscription and recurring transaction needs in Magento</description>
                    <pay_label>Learn More</pay_label>
                    <pay_url>https://powersync.biz/subscription-management-solution</pay_url>
                </TNW_Subscriptions>
                <TNW_Salesforce>
                    <label>Salesforce integration for Magento</label>
                    <img_name>salesforce_integration.png</img_name>
                    <description>Connects your Magento store with your Salesforce CRM, integrating all of your store data</description>
                    <pay_label>Learn More</pay_label>
                    <pay_url>https://powersync.biz/magento-and-salesforce-integration</pay_url>
                </TNW_Salesforce>
                <TNW_QuickbooksBasic>
                    <label>QuickBooks Online</label>
                    <img_name>quickbooks.png</img_name>
                    <description>Close the gap to ensure complete and accurate accounting when using QuickBooks Online and Magento 2 platform</description>
                    <pay_label>Try it for FREE</pay_label>
                    <pay_url>https://powersync.biz/free-integrations-for-magento2?products=QuickBooks%20Integration%20Starter%20Pack</pay_url>
                </TNW_QuickbooksBasic>
                <TNW_Stripe>
                    <label>Stripe Integration</label>
                    <img_name>stripe.png</img_name>
                    <description>Accept credit card payments using Stripe payment gateway. Allow customers to save cards for their next purchase.</description>
                    <pay_label>Learn More</pay_label>
                    <pay_url>https://powersync.biz/free-integrations-for-magento2?products=Stripe%20Payment%20Gateway%20Integration</pay_url>
                </TNW_Stripe>
                <TNW_AuthorizeCim>
                    <label>Authorize.Net CIM</label>
                    <img_name>authorize.png</img_name>
                    <description>Accept credit card payments using Authorize.Net payment gateway. Allow customers to save cards for their next purchase.</description>
                    <pay_label>Try it for FREE</pay_label>
                    <pay_url>https://powersync.biz/free-integrations-for-magento2?products=Authorize.Net%20CIM%20Payment%20Integration</pay_url>
                </TNW_AuthorizeCim>
            </products>
            <promotions>
                <TNW_Subscriptions>
                    <applicable_routes>catalog_product_index,sales_order_index,quotes_quote_index</applicable_routes>
                    <url>https://technweb.com/subscription-management-and-recurring-billing-for-magento</url>
                    <title>Turn Repeat Buyers into Reliable Revenue with Subscriptions</title>
                    <button_text>Learn More</button_text>
                    <full_description>
                        <![CDATA[
                        <p>Build a consistent, predictable revenue stream by offering subscriptions for the products or services your customers purchase most often. Our solution is natively integrated with Adobe Commerce (Magento) and designed for flexibility, scale, and security.</p>
                            <ul>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i>Seamlessly <b>track and manage subscriptions</b> within Adobe Commerce</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>Highly flexible and robust,</b> backed by customer testimonials</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i>Fully supports <b>Cart Price Rules</b> and <b>Catalog Price Rules</b></li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i>Compatible with <b>Stripe, PayPal, Braintree, <a href="https://www.authorize.net/">Authorize.Net</a>, CyberSource,</b> and all Magento-supported offline payment methods</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i>Easily integrates with <b>additional payment gateways</b></li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>PCI-compliant,</b> leveraging Adobe Commerce Vault for secure data storage</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i>Includes <b>pre-built email templates</b> for customer notifications</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i>Native support for <b><a href="https://link.technweb.com/425VlSi">Bills</a></b> in Adobe Commerce</li>
                            </ul>
                            <p>Whether you’re offering <b>memberships, auto-shipments,</b> or <b>recurring subscriptions,</b> this solution helps you retain loyal customers and never miss a sale.</p>
                        ]]>
                    </full_description>
                </TNW_Subscriptions>
                <TNW_VendorInvoice>
                    <applicable_routes>sales_invoice_index</applicable_routes>
                    <url>https://link.technweb.com/425VlSi</url>
                    <title>Simplify Invoicing and Vendor Billing in Adobe Commerce</title>
                    <button_text>Learn More</button_text>
                    <full_description>
                        <![CDATA[
                            <p>Seamlessly send invoices to customers and bills to vendors — directly within your Adobe Commerce platform. Automate late fees, reminders, and payment collection with powerful, built-in invoice management tools.</p>
                            <ul>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>Flexible NET Terms</b> for tailored payment schedules</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>Automated Invoice Reminders</b> to reduce manual follow-up</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>Automatic Payment Collection</b> via Credit Card and ACH</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>Pre-Built Email Templates</b> for consistent, professional communication</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>Global & Customer-Specific Settings</b> to fit your business needs</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>PDF Invoice Attachments</b> included with every email</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>Customizable Invoice Prefixes</b> and Numbering for easy tracking</li>
                            </ul>
                            <p>Take control of your receivables with a smart, scalable invoicing solution—fully integrated into Adobe Commerce.</p>
                        ]]>
                    </full_description>
                </TNW_VendorInvoice>
                <TNW_Stripe>
                    <applicable_routes>adminhtml_integration_index</applicable_routes>
                    <url>https://technweb.com/magento-stripe-payment-integration</url>
                    <title>Stripe Integration</title>
                    <button_text>FREE Download</button_text>
                    <full_description>
                        <![CDATA[
                            <p>Enable secure, seamless payments on your website with our <b>FREE Stripe Payment Gateway Integration</b>. This PCI-compliant solution allows your customers to safely purchase products and services online, directly through your Adobe Commerce store.</p>
                            <p>Proudly offered as a complimentary product by <b>TechNWeb, Inc.</b> in collaboration with the <b>Magento community</b>.</p>
                        ]]>
                    </full_description>
                </TNW_Stripe>
                <TNW_AuthorizeCim>
                    <applicable_routes>adminhtml_integration_index</applicable_routes>
                    <url>https://technweb.com/magento-authorize-net-payment-integration</url>
                    <title>Authorize.Net CIM Integration</title>
                    <button_text>FREE Download</button_text>
                    <full_description>
                        <![CDATA[
                            <p>Offer your customers a secure, seamless checkout experience with our <b>FREE <a href="https://www.authorize.net/">Authorize.Net</a> Payment Gateway Integration</b>. This PCI-compliant solution enables safe online payments for your products and services—fully integrated with Adobe Commerce (Magento).</p>
                            <p>Provided at no cost by <b>TechNWeb, Inc.</b> in partnership with the <b>Magento community</b>.</p>
                        ]]>
                    </full_description>
                </TNW_AuthorizeCim>
                <TNW_Salesforce>
                    <applicable_routes>adminhtml_integration_index,customer_index_index,adminhtml_export_index,company_index_index,catalog_product_index,sales_order_index,sales_invoice_index,quotes_quote_index</applicable_routes>
                    <url>https://idealdata.io/lp/magento-crm-integration</url>
                    <title>Integrate with your CRM</title>
                    <button_text>FREE Trial</button_text>
                    <full_description>
                        <![CDATA[
                            <p>Integrating your Adobe Commerce platform with a Customer Relationship Management (CRM) system can significantly enhance your business operations by automating processes, reducing errors, and providing comprehensive customer insights.</p>
                            <p><a href="https://idealdata.io/">Ideal Data:</a> eCommerce Integration Platform  specializes in seamless Magento-CRM integrations, delivering tangible benefits:</p>
                            <ul>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>Increased Sales:</b> Achieve up to a 25% close rate on abandoned cart deals through automated recovery strategies.</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>Operational Efficiency:</b> Eliminate manual errors with automated product synchronization between your store and your CRM.</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>Real-Time Analytics:</b> Access revenue dashboards for instant sales tracking and informed decision-making.</li>
                                <li><i class="fa fa-li fa-check-circle-o"></i><b>Personalized Marketing:</b> Utilize data-driven insights to craft targeted marketing campaigns that resonate with your audience.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <p>Discover how <a href="https://idealdata.io/">Ideal Data:</a> eCommerce Integration Platform  can transform your sales and marketing efforts by seamlessly connecting Adobe Commerce platform with your CRM.</p>
                        ]]>
                    </full_description>
                </TNW_Salesforce>
            </promotions>
        </marketing>
    </default>
</config>
